weird time,
possibly for writing books, because
there is this idea that nobody needs
to write books anymore,
now that we've got AI,
AI will write the books for us,
and I think that is,
to use a technical term here,
bullshit,
and when I say technical
term, I mean a technical term.
Bullshit is something that the
people who are telling you don't care
whether it's true or not.
And the people who are telling you
that you don't need to write anything
anymore, AI will do it all for you,
are the AI companies and the bosses.
So the AI companies and the bosses
are saying this because they don't
want to pay people to do things.
And the AI companies are telling the
bosses this because they want the
bosses to buy AI. They're kind of
saying, look, buy AI and then you
won't have to employ any people
anymore.
And the AI, the AI, and the AI
companies want people who actually write
books to believe this because they
want the people who actually create
things to be depressed and scared
so that they can steal things off
those people cheaply.